Ana Bogatinovska

+38972207429 bogatinovska.ana@gmail.com Web Presence
LinkedIn
Github
Ana's Personal Portfolio & Resume

Ana Bogatinovska Software Engineer

ABOUT ME

I am a dedicated Software Engineer with solid experience in building user-friendly, responsive web and mobile interfaces. My technical expertise includes JavaScript, TypeScript, Angular, Dart, and Flutter, among other modern frameworks. I excel at problem-solving, tackling new challenges with enthusiasm, and ensuring effective communication within diverse teams. My goal is to drive digital projects that make a significant, positive impact.

SKILLS

- Javascript, Typescript, Angular 13+, Dart, Flutter, Ionic Framework,
 Vuejs, Reactjs, Quasar Framework
- AWS Amplify Auth, Rxjs, Fuse Angular Template, Tailwind, Angular Material, YouTrack, Trello GitHub, GraphQL
- NgRx Store, MongoDb, LocalStorage, Vuex store

EXPERIENCE

MFactor Consultancy - Melbourne, Australia — *Software Engineer*

December 2021 - present (Remote)

- Developed user-friendly responsive web & mobile interfaces
- Code reviews, identify bugs, implement necessary fixes and improvements
- Close communication with backend developers and designers
- Skills: Javascript, TypeScript, Angular 13+, Angular Material, Tailwind,
 Fuse Angular, Flutter, Ionic Framework, GitHib, YouTrack, Trello, Vue 2,
 RxJs, NgRx Store, Vuex Store

Musala Soft - Skopje, North Macedonia — Junior Software Engineer

April 2021 - November 2021- 8 mos (Work from anywhere)

- Worked on company internal web application
- Involved in a project for developing FloorPlan.
- Skills: Javascript, TypeScript, Angular 12+, Vue 2, RxJs, NgRx Store, Vuex Store

FX3X - Skopje, North Macedonia— Vfx Roto Artist

August 2015 - May 2020 - 4 yrs 9 mos (On-site)

- Roto animation of movie footage from a given deadline.
- Proficiency in team work.
- Successful completion of the work within a given deadline.

EDUCATION

High School 'Pance Arsovski' - Skopje, North Macedonia

September 2008 - June 2012, Skopje

Online course for Frontend Web Developer - Skopje, North Macedonia

October 2020 - December 2020, FINKI - Skopje

PROJECTS

- <u>Annadaan Ammucare</u> Food donations for people or animals across India. Front end technologies: Javascript, Typescript, Angular/Ionic Framework
 - Web: <u>annadaan.ammucare</u>, Google Play Store: <u>annadaan.ammucare</u>
 - App Store: <u>annadaan.ammucare</u>
- Act 4 Hunger Food Donation ACT 4 Hunger (A4H) is a global charitable platform that serves food to the hungry. Front end technologies: Flutter(Dart), Riverpod
 - Google Play Store: act4hunger
 - App Store: <u>act4hunger</u>
- Reztor Renovation This project provides a powerful tool for managing jobs, assigning tasks, generating quotes and invoices, and to create perfect communication between team members. Front end technologies: Angular, Fuse Template, Tailwind CSS
- Serve Swiftly Building SaaS platform for restaurants, bars and similar companies in the Food & Beverages industry to reinvent the way they do order management. Some of the core features were orders, employee, work shift and product management. Front end

technologies: Flutter(Dart), Riverpod

• PULZ - Web project which is an Admin portal where doctors can login and review a patient's heart health history and download or preview raw ECG data for further processing and analysis.